# **Amanda Kautzky**

(206) 387-6866 – amanda.kautzky@gmail.com

# **Qualifications Profile:**

Highly motivated, solutions focused professional with extensive experience and impressive customer service within many roles.

Exceptional interpersonal communication skills with proficiency to promote confidence and build and maintain strategic business/client relationships while interfacing positivity with people of diverse backgrounds.

# **Professional Experience:**

### **Amazon- Prime Video**

September 2021 – Present

Program Manager- Mike Fazzino, Seattle, WA

Manage content submitted through Prime Video Direct

Track decision, operator, and genre in WBR and MBR

Manage solicited non-fiction content and coordinate with content acquisition managers

Research and report competition content gaps

## **Amazon- Delivery Experience**

*July* 2019 – *September* 2021

Marketing Specialist I- Faviola Iglesias, Seattle, WA

Certified as a Content Bar Raiser

Develop and maintain marketing campaigns for Bargain Finds in US, EU, and JP

Curate and refresh Bargain Finds product list

Draft process and lead as subject matter expert for email campaigns

# **Amazon- Fulfillment by Amazon**

June 2018 – July 2019

Sr. Investigations Specialist – Amy Morales, Seattle, WA

Assist on special projects that design/improve tools or processes by testing and/or development

Draft and schedule individual merchandising campaigns to category homepages

Conduct data analytic deep dives to measure the performance of the content produced

Provide input and research to optimize marketing messaging worldwide

### **Amazon- Fulfillment by Amazon**

*September 2016 – June 2018* 

Investigations Specialist - Amy Morales, Seattle, WA

Identify root cause defects that lead to reduction in inbound

Adhere to standard operating procedures to correct identified defects

Coordinate with seller support to mitigate risks in internal operations

Build summary metrics to management

Provide additional support in project work outside of regular work duties

# **Blueprint Consulting Services**

August 2015 – September 2016

Team Lead – Ray Flores, Bellevue, WA

Advanced from tech to subject matter expert to team lead

Support the Chinese team and expand skills in the operations space

Build and maintain documentation on Chinese support training

Maintain schedules and KPI's

Prepare and lead team status meetings

## **Education:**

North Seattle College Seattle, WA

Pursuing Associate in Computer Science, Graduation 2024

University of Washington Seattle, WA

Certificate in project management, 2016

Eastlake High School Sammamish, WA

High school diploma, 2010